Resume

Basic Info.

Name: Calvin Li Gender: Male

Date of Birth: 1983/1/13 Citizenship: USA

Yrs.of Experience: 5 years

Email: realcal113@gmail.com

Mobile Phone:

626-537-5719

**Self Assessment** 

Nearly 5 years of commercial real estate and retail experience in Asia (Shanghai, China)

market, not only builds up my professional skills to handle and achieve all the tasks strong

and efficiently. It also definitely helps me to think outside of the box and bring some fresh

blood to the company. Negotiating and operating with both retail and F&B tenants gives me

the ability to professionally work with all kinds of clients at work. Strategic planning for

shopping malls, complex projects, and outlets is an other skill I build up during previous work.

**Work Experience** 

2013/8-2014/5

RDM Management Consulting(Beijing) Company Limited Shanghai Branch (100-500 people)

**Industry: Commercial Real Estate** 

Leasing

Manager

Experience:

Responsible for Retail and F&B leasing activities for outlet project in Shanghai

1.term negotiation, contract signing, and follow up till shop open.

2. Deal with brands such as KFC, Pizza Hut, Starbucks, Haggen Dazs, Subway, Friday, Element

Fresh, McDonald, some local franchise Chinese restaurants, and fashion retail brands such as

CK Jeans, CK Underwear, Ecco, Puma, TAG Heuer, Eland Group and etc.

3. working with design, construction company and tenants to meet the shop requirement

4. Assist tenant to visit project site

5. Help to make better operation plan for Wuqing project

6. Looking for potential new tenant for Wuqing project and help company generate better

incomes

7. Participated in the Guangzhou project launch event

2010/12-2013/8

Chia Tai Group-Super Brand Mall(500-1000 people)

Industry: Commercial Real Estate

Leasing Manager

Experience:

1. Anchor store and Food & Beverage leasing for Chia Tai Touch Mall. Negotiated with Mark

& Spencer, South Beauty, Guang Zhou Banana Leaf, Daikanyama, BiFengTang, KFC, Ajisen,

coco curry house. Coordinate with construction, design, tenant coordinate department. The

project will be grand open in April. 2013.

2. Superbrand Mall Qing Dao Jimo Project. Responsible for the early market research,

project business format, floor plan, internal circulation flow and so on. The estimate opening

time for this project will be in year 2015.

3. Superbrand Mall He Nan Luo Yang Project. Participated in the overall project planning,

including coordinate with third party market research company.

4. Superbrand Mall Guang Zhou Tian He project. This project is owned by LOTUS under Chia

Tai Group, participated in overall project planning and discussion within the group.

5. Superbrand Mall Bei Jing CBD project. Market research and early stage tenant negotiation.

6. Superbrand Mall He Fei project. Participated in the renovation project, including working

with DTZ for market research reports. This is an renovation project which will increase the

area from 25 thousand square meters to 220 thousand square meters, and will become one

of the landmark in He Fei new economic district. Currently working on floor plans and brand

targeting.

7. Chia Tai Group's new project's early stage planning (business format ration, brand

targeting, coordinate with world top design company: Benoy, Gensler, RTKL)

8. Leasing area of 72 LOTUS hypermarkets under Chia Tai group nationwide, and responsible

for daily leasing tasks and customer relation with KFC, Ajisen, Pizza Hut.

**20**08/5—**20**10/11

iSoftstone(500-1000 people)

**Industry: technology consulting** 

**Test Engineer** 

Experience:

Web application testing for enterprise like Microsoft Shanghai, General Motor China, Shanghai Bell Alcatel Lucent.

## **Education**

2002/9 -- 2007/12 California State University of Pomona Electrical Engineering and

Automation Bachelor

## **Language Skills**

English(Excellent): Listening&Speaking(Excellent) , Reading&Writing(Excellent)

<u>Chinese Mandarin(Excellent)</u>: <u>Listening&Speaking(Excellent)</u>, <u>Reading&Writing(Excellent)</u>